Yastrebov Andrey

me@yastrebov.com Skype: <u>yastrebov3</u>

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/ayastrebov

Github: github.com/Ayastrebov

Facebook: <u>facebook.com/AndrewYastrebov</u>

Summary

iOS app developer (including iPhone, iPad, iPod Touch) with five year experience in mobile application design and development. Used to develop both, mobile games and apps with complex business-logic. My goal is to create mobile software with high-performance and easily maintainable codebase on top of clean and useable UI. I am constantly learning new technologies and always try to improve my skills in this rapidly changing industry. I've also contributed in some open-source projects, and stay in touch with other interesting community projects.

Technical Skills

Languages: Objective-C; Java; Python; Lua

Development Software: Xcode; Eclipse; AppCode IntelliJ IDEA; Netbeans;

Sublime text; PyCharm; Git; Svn

Technologies: RESTfull web services; JSON; XML; iOS Core Services; Cocos2D; CoreData; RestKit; AFNetworking; Corona; Cocoapods; OAuth;

Facebook API; Twitter API; VK API; Odnoklassniki API

Platforms: OS X; Linux; iOS; Android **Cloud Services:** Parse; Heroku; Github

Work Experience

Agile Fusion Corporation as a iOS Software Engineer since July 2012 to present time (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

- 1. Shelvz iOS app for redeeming coupons in various US stores
- 2. Jack and Jill iOS game for kids, made with corona SDK
- 3. Fleapop iOS app. Mobile Flea market shopping
- 4. Regivit iOS shopping app, similar to eBay
- 5. ThatInbox iOS mail app, which utilizes mailcore2 library and INK

frameworks

- 6. Mobile Appointments iOS app which integrates with build-in calendar app
- 7. Active Learning iOS app for reading, browsing and purchasing epub books
- 8. Chefs Feed iOS app, the first and only chef-powered restaurant guide.

FoodMap LLC as a iOS and Android Software Engineer since May 2011 to June 2012 (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

1.Menutka — iOS and Android app for spotting nearest cafes and restaurants and provides a full menu with a social integration.

Lanit-Tercom as a iOS Software Engineer since September 2010 to May 2011 (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

- 1. Hunting pro iOS app for patterning a shotgun
- 2. Cafes Network iOS app (branded) for cafes. Allowing people to get new friendships in the particular cafe.
- 3. Recorder app iOS voice recording app with speex codec support

Independent & Contract iOS Development since January 2009 to September 2010 (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

- 1. Various casual games, made with Cocos2D framework
- 2. Multiple iOS utility apps (one of them was top-3 Russian AppStore)
- 3. Freelance projects

Education

Saint-Petersburg State University Mathematics and Mechanics Faculty Specialist degree since 2006 to 2012